nimblecommerce.com 2019-07-18

# NimbleCommerce - Group Buying and Local Commerce Platform

NimbleCommerce Privacy Statement 

### Data Privacy at NimbleCommerce

NimbleCommerce has established a comprehensive privacy program, including a global privacy office and a chief privacy officer, designed to help us respect and protect your data privacy rights. This statement includes both NimbleCommerce's European Union - U.S. Safe Harbor Privacy Statement and the Website Privacy Statement. 

### U.S. - EU Safe Harbor Privacy Statement

For personal information of employees and customers that NimbleCommerce receives from the European Economic Area, NimbleCommerce has committed to handling such personal information in accordance with the Safe Harbor Principles. NimbleCommerce's Safe Harbor certification can be found at [ http://web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/shlist.nsf/webPages/safe+harbor+list ](http://web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/shlist.nsf/webPages/safe+harbor+list). For more information about the Safe Harbor Principles, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Website at [ http://export.gov/safeharbor/ ](http://export.gov/safeharbor/). 

###  NimbleCommerce Website Privacy Statement 

NimbleCommerce respects the privacy of visitors to its websites, as a result, we have developed this website privacy policy. This website privacy policy applies only to the operation of websites that directly link to this policy when you click on "privacy statement" in the website footer. 

We require people who register to use a NimbleCommerce online application (the "Services") to give us contact information. Depending on the services chosen, we ask for contact and account information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, e-mail address, password and the number of users in the organization who will be using the Services, in addition to financial and billing information, such as billing name, address and credit card number. 

We may also use Your Information to contact you and/or provide you with general information as well as information about our products and services. We may also enhance or merge Your Information with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes. 

Any other information transferred by you in connection with your visit to this site ("Other Information" - that is, information that cannot be used to identify you) may be included in databases owned and maintained by NimbleCommerce or its agents. NimbleCommerce retains all rights to these databases and the information contained in them. Other Information we collect may include your IP Address and other information gathered through our weblogs and cookies (see below). 

This site may use a technology known as web beacons - sometimes called single- pixel gifs - that allow this site to collect web log information. A web beacon is a graphic on a web page or in an e-mail message designed to track pages viewed or messages opened. Web log information is gathered when you visit one of our websites by the computer that hosts our website (called a "webserver"). The webserver automatically recognizes some non-personal information, such as the date and time you visited our site, the pages you visited, the website you came from, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows), and the domain name and address of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast). We may also include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages in order to determine whether messages have been opened. 

This website may use a technology called a "cookie". A cookie is a piece of in- formation that our webserver sends to your computer (actually to your browser file) when you access a website. Then when you come back our site will detect whether you have one of our cookies on your computer. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the site and help us analyze site usage more accurately. For instance, our site may set a cookie on your browser that keeps you from needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the site. 

We do not allow third parties to collect your personally identifiable information or track your actions through cookies and web beacons over time and across different websites or platforms. 

In addition, you may be able to adjust your browser settings or other settings so that “do not track” requests are sent to the websites and mobile applications that you use. However, NimbleCommerce will not disable tracking technology that may be active on this website in response to any “do not track” requests that are sent to the website. 

This website uses Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet. Generally, an IP address changes each time you connect to the Internet (it is a "dynamic" address). Note, however, that if you have a broadband connection, depending on your individual circumstance, it is possible that your IP Address that we collect, or even perhaps a cookie we use, may contain information that could be deemed identifiable. This is because with some broadband connections your IP Address doesn't change (it is "static") and could be associated with your personal computer. We use your IP address to report aggregate information on use and to help improve the website. 

NimbleCommerce uses a persistent encrypted cookie, if the client requests, to save and retrieve individual authentication information as well as other per-client device preferences. When a visitor follows a link to the NimbleCommerce Web site from an affiliate or promotion, NimbleCommerce stores information about that affiliate or promotion in a session cookie. Acceptance of these cookies is optional. NimbleCommerce issues a mandatory session cookie to each user of the Services only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of a specific session. If you reject this cookie, access to and usage of the Services will be denied. 

You should be aware that this site is not intended for, or designed to attract, individuals under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is an individual under the age of 18.

NimbleCommerce has security measures in place for the Services to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the data under NimbleCommerce's control. When the Services are accessed using Netscape Navigator, or Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 4.0 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure data is safe, secure and available only to you. NimbleCommerce also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications and hosts the Services in a secure server environment using a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Finally, NimbleCommerce requires unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a customer logs on. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of data.

We may share Your Information with agents, contractors or partners of NimbleCommerce in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for, or with, NimbleCommerce. These agents, contractors or partners are restricted from using this data in any way other than to provide services for NimbleCommerce, or services for the collaboration in which they and NimbleCommerce are engaged. For example, NimbleCommerce uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain and is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided, except for the sole purpose of credit card processing.

NimbleCommerce reserves the right to share Your Information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities or where required by law. In exceptionally rare circumstances where national, state or company security is at issue, NimbleCommerce reserves the right to share our entire database of visitors and customers with appropriate governmental authorities.

We may also provide Your Information to a third party in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this website to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat Your Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

As a convenience to our visitors, this Website currently contains links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy, security, data collection, and distribution policies.

NimbleCommerce offers you a means to choose how we may use information you provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering the Services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing information with third parties, send us a request specifying your new choice. Send your request to support@nimblecommerce.com. 

### Correcting and Updating Your Information

To update or change registration information, to update billing information, or to discontinue the Services, log on to the Services at a NimbleCommerce Web site, click the Setup tab, and click links to these tasks. You can also correct and update information by e-mailing [DL-HawkCommerceProdErrors@bhnetwork.com](mailto:DL-HawkCommerceProdErrors@bhnetwork.com). 

###  Additional Information 

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the security practices of the Services should be directed to NimbleCommerce's Security Administrator by e-mailing [security@nimblecommerce.com](mailto:security@nimblecommerce.com). 

To be removed from our contact lists, please write to NimbleCommerce at the following address: 

NimbleCommerce   
Attn. Privacy Officer   
4699 Old Ironsides Dr. Suite 450   
Santa Clara, CA. 95054 USA   

Please note that you may continue to receive materials while we are updating our lists. 

We may update this Web site Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do update it, for your convenience, we will make the updated policy available on this page. 

Last Updated: January 22, 2016
